ID,lang,sent,labels
fc76cef4-3a91-4394-b6d4-be7c4ed840d5,train,"his  playlist  includes  sonny  sharrock  ,  gza  ,  country  teasers  and  the  notorious  b.i.g. ", O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-PER  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER
ff57d715-80cc-4fb2-9444-901a55ad5dc1,train,"it  is  a  series  of  badminton  tournaments  ,  sanctioned  by  badminton  world  federation  (  bwf  )  since  2007  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O
f1f78d1e-1d16-41fd-a9b3-52559949b11c,train,"all  songs  written  by  m.o.d.  ,  unless  otherwise  stated ", O  O  O  O  B-GRP  O  O  O  O
aacf70c5-dec4-4b8f-836e-ba2c4607de39,train,"he  worked  in  a  bookstore  before  becoming  a  journalist  ,  first  for  le  devoir  ,  and  then  for  cité  libre  ,  for  which  he  later  became  the  director  . ", O  O  O  O  B-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
5806a9e5-0c0a-4850-8148-c3151359b2f9,train,rinder  did  not  speak  on  camera  because  he  promised  his  first  interview  to  the  bbc  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O
37495040-c9c9-437f-aa23-90ad96b89d8f,train,indigenous  outlaw  musquito  defied  colonial  law  and  led  attacks  on  settlers  . , O  O  B-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
a52dd345-0ad8-40a7-88a5-5053fc80a23d,train,a  code  generation  usually  converts  some  intermediate  representation  of  source  code  into  machine  code  . , O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
a97f0d75-57e7-4a16-b956-d70525bbc2c5,train,the  main  contractor  was  ssangyong  engineering  and  construction  . , O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O
f6d6a381-5ed0-423c-8076-63659fbea283,train,"in  2010  ,  the  musical  instrument  maestro  raghav  sachar  was  the  highlight  of  the  event  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
bf8790c4-3cf9-4c17-82f0-1e02a1f8b0c3,train,she  became  opposed  to  abortion  in  1992  while  attending  a  bible  study  and  has  since  spoken  out  about  how  abortion  has  negatively  impacted  her  life  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
f118c528-430f-4063-b621-f36ad56c217e,train,france  proletarian  unity  party  (  pup  )  (  from  1933  ) , O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
494a05a9-0fa5-414f-b57c-8c455677cfc7,train,"for  example  ,  in  one  advertisement  a  woman  wearing  a  yellow  shirt  and  a  pin  is  juxtaposed  with  a  similarly  colored  piece  of  pie  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O
130ab99c-65d5-40a0-b996-5187c9b0c7ab,train,the  guardian  described  the  album  's  release  as  one  of  the  50  key  events  in  the  history  of  r&b  and  hip  hop  . , B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
2e684f84-58a3-456c-8c07-fe600866d25c,train,"the  crew  intended  the  movie  to  be  a  continuation  of  the  season  five  finale  the  end  ,  but  was  also  meant  to  stand  on  its  own  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
40edbb1f-d9c3-46d3-ba13-c649a737083d,train,"the  gameplay  has  been  described  as  action  heavy  ,  and  compared  to  the  ratchet  &  clank  series  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O
396f521a-fd9c-4b74-94e4-11e327af1c2e,train,mingus  left  in  1951  and  red  mitchell  replaced  him  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O
4bf88485-0239-48b5-ae9e-ab27d89dd3b9,train,american  weekly  radio  show  wait  wait...  don't  tell  me!  was  started  in  1998  on  public  radio  network  npr  . , O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O
cc713d03-fe96-438f-8f66-25dd45c6cfa8,train,hanna  died  in  st.  george  in  2019  at  the  age  of  90  . , O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
005a6790-233d-4c5f-95d0-5292957bba8f,train,"it  was  developed  by  a  team  led  by  former  blizzard  entertainment  employees  ,  some  of  whom  had  overseen  the  creation  of  the  diablo  series  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O
92a66f8a-7365-4631-a745-f8e8e054a034,train,"in  the  winter  months  ,  snowmobile  is  also  popular  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O
cb42a990-f48d-489d-a734-d36e97b1cc6d,train,black  swan  (  co  production  with  cross  creek  pictures  and  phoenix  pictures  ) , B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
895ab3ff-2bb9-43e0-a85e-4679cb40e399,train,the  play  interweaves  the  lives  of  the  poet  w.  h.  auden  and  the  mathematician  alan  turing  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
59e19ca3-ebc9-4762-b71c-6d25c92e03f8,train,"the  1988  elections  were  also  held  on  a  non  party  basis  ,  although  around  30  candidates  sympathetic  to  the  muslim  brotherhood  were  elected  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O
dbb3e457-74dd-4add-8068-f98145aa7ee8,train,she  fronted  the  band  gossip  from  its  formation  in  1999  until  its  dissolution  in  2016  . , O  O  O  O  B-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
386ec660-9bf0-4784-b2f8-8d076b9fae0c,train,a  european  union  directive  which  covers  high  visibility  clothing  . , O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
242b4300-1709-467d-9343-8ae6174aff4b,train,the  game  uses  a  battery  packed  random-access  memory  in  order  to  save  progress  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O
097c3dbe-09ff-4dd0-93dd-60f6aafe94d0,train,in  the  end  the  best  placed  rider  was  wilfried  cretskens  who  finished  61st  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O
e78bcb79-52ad-4938-b75c-d19d4dfce4e8,train,"of  the  429  delegates  who  attended  ,  over  one  third  were  from  the  area  around  wheeling  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O
7ad6b87a-80aa-478f-9d98-2e914707cccd,train,"in  doing  so  ,  he  reunited  with  former  high  school  and  college  teammate  malik  jackson  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
58d12e07-bb65-45bd-9511-0f6da66aca37,train,"modelled  for  yves  saint  laurent  ,  versace  ,  and  karl  lagerfeld  . ", O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  B-CORP  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
09defc13-be3a-44b8-9f74-f071d618c867,train,,
fd6767db-12e0-4748-b469-f66c6ccb9557,train,there  remained  the  question  of  whether  the  improved  performance  compared  to  the  automated  kh-8  gambit  3  satellite  then  under  development  justified  the  cost  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
d9a0350b-2d3f-4302-a760-376c045e7dea,train,"the  group  smith  recorded  a  version  on  their  1969  debut  album  ,  sung  by  gayle  mccormick ", O  O  B-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER
f6285e99-68b2-49cf-a821-16756d558195,train,"bamboo  ,  like  wood  ,  is  a  natural  composite  material  with  a  high  strength  to  weight  ratio  useful  for  structures  . ", O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
1dd73a26-35ee-4260-8bcc-f7874f077ae1,train,in  previous  years  he  had  worked  with  alex  cox  on  the  soundtracks  of  his  films  sid  and  nancy  and  walker  in  1986  and  1987  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O
7e4138f8-3391-4bf6-81ac-b0e5c5feab89,train,"historian  françois  furet  was  originally  slated  to  write  the  introduction  ,  but  he  died  before  being  able  to  do  so  . ", O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
289173e8-83d0-4d83-a4f8-3ba00d642ed1,train,it  is  the  main  hub  of  fiji  airways  and  its  domestic  and  regional  subsidiary  fiji  link  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
46806e1d-aea8-421b-b371-9cebdc62d8dd,train,"it  was  broadcast  on  the  channel  animal  planet  ,  with  episodes  having  aired  between  2001  and  2003  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
5af1184f-774f-4de4-bd2c-2af3e45ed174,train,"it  stars  jeetendra  ,  moushumi  chatterjee  ,  govinda  ,  shilpa  shirodkar  with  music  composed  by  rajesh  roshan  . ", O  O  B-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
fc807a98-9e22-4327-be34-6f7d043272a7,train,variety  suggested  that  the  mid  may  opening  date  was  overshadowed  by  the  socko  b.o.  of  ip  man  2  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O
93e529ae-fb68-4712-acec-500ed2cd7f72,train,"he  picked  up  his  dad  ’s  banjo  at  age  8  and  by  the  time  he  was  11  ,  he  had  a  gibson  banjo  endorsement  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  O  O
202758e3-79b7-4725-bbea-d7a455291c85,train,a  term  loan  is  a  monetary  loan  that  is  repaid  in  regular  payments  over  a  set  period  of  time  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
f1b548cf-c005-43a1-b1eb-596204d5d19b,train,"then  he  became  a  salesman  ,  and  later  a  public  relations  consultant  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O
dcfe2620-dbc6-41e5-9f9b-7f12455a9eec,train,"riccardo  ghedin  /  stéphane  robert  def  .  arnaud  clément  /  olivier  rochus  ,  6  –  2  ,  5  –  7  ,  [  10  –  7  ] ", B-PER  I-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
c09807db-853f-4789-8006-57b268a1bca6,train,"many  buildings  were  built  in  a  brick  nonplastering  style  characterized  by  a  special  kind  of  decorative  arts  using  colored  ,  figured  bricks  ,  usually  yellow  and  red  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
aa268db3-5cb9-4d00-816d-ff380b19a80f,train,"is  a  juku  in  tokyo  ,  established  over  300  years  ago  . ", O  O  B-CORP  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
41eedba2-d3e4-4d43-9cbb-0ad9c72a52b0,train,the  city  is  also  home  to  via  university  college  which  brings  a  lot  of  international  students  to  move  to  this  town  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
b4e603bc-d944-48c8-bef8-5506a3e65a25,train,fleur  live  stenogram  and  recording  at  echo  of  moscow  (  rus  ) , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O
14689355-ed37-44ff-8df2-d802cb7b9834,train,"refrigerator  ,  a  device  used  to  cool  objects  or  interior  spaces ", B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
a7c3eea1-8687-4cc8-9c97-f1f23cb36c1a,train,"in  1920  ,  she  accompanied  her  father  to  rio  de  janeiro  and  são  paulo  ,  where  she  was  well  received  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
9610b08c-b105-492f-876b-794b15a1e15a,train,"vanadzor  (  )  is  an  urban  municipal  community  and  the  third  largest  city  in  armenia  ,  serving  as  the  capital  of  lori  region  in  the  northern  part  of  the  country  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
e8724c98-328e-40b6-bc8e-cc0b09c720da,train,"lauren  jackson  has  won  the  award  four  times  ,  while  kelsey  griffin  has  won  the  award  three  times  . ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
abe88e39-d835-4f9b-b25a-5a9c50ee5a79,train,"401  designates  a  373  cc  engine  ,  derived  from  the  ktm  390  duke  of  street  bikes ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O
2a0ea54c-e5f2-4595-b499-e823fecc2778,train,"oakland  's  defense  ,  anchored  by  defensive  end  john  matuszak  ,  was  punishing  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O
e03f618a-03de-456d-a795-2a72e8a8601e,train,"recipes  vary  slightly  ,  but  the  dish  is  basically  crème  caramel  made  out  of  eggs  and  sweetened  milk  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
7119f8c3-f585-4138-b28c-f1dda07bb154,train,,
c8e2d38c-77ef-4067-8554-c94881bbf135,train,"however  she  has  to  settle  for  silver  medal  after  she  lost  to  akane  yamaguchi  in  a  tightly  contested  final  match  of  3  games  21  –  14  ,  18  –  21  ,  13  –  21  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
11df49ff-22ec-440a-bdcb-feeae2796635,train,david  foster  wallace  2011  novel  the  pale  king  alludes  to  the  poem  in  its  title  . , B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
39de9d51-b754-47a2-bf71-a0fdbfad95b3,train,one  maglite  of  rechargeable  focusing  flashlight  uses  a  halogen  lamp  and  produces  218  lumens  . , O  B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
aa19875b-ef2e-482d-adb6-4d8a9d73a81b,train,"afs  intercultural  programs  international  youth  exchange  program  ,  founded  in  1915 ", B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
31474e3e-744e-48de-8ee4-ab4c51fa3c05,train,the  natural  and  architectural  ensemble  of  stolac , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC
44ecedb1-d6f3-4801-8b89-b7a82aacfc31,train,it  was  also  used  in  the  netflix  series  stranger  things  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  B-CW  I-CW  O
b1a4bf9e-3040-4909-8220-5b144b94ad0b,train,"she  is  a  card  carrying  geek  and  considers  herself  boy  proof  ,  and  proud  of  it  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
9df84a6a-fbf8-4443-b4f5-68988c7a2298,train,"is  a  tactical  role-playing  game  for  the  playstation  ,  developed  and  published  by  namco  . ", O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O
53471bc1-7bd0-4a5f-8042-c50eb1c76c77,train,he  is  the  co  founder  and  president  of  greentown  china  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
2d4c03e6-2008-48da-bd5b-ac8a0e7f11d5,train,he  played  4  games  for  the  united  rugby  championship  club  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O
a8a188e1-680d-4ca3-92db-3efd222b1096,train,"the  philosopher  and  historian  ,  władysław  tatarkiewicz  ,  was  his  grandson  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O
f853ae21-b018-4382-a767-816ba07f9bd6,train,"duo  ,  with  michael  wollny  (  piano  )  ;  in  concert ", O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O
3833c877-f888-4713-a4c3-40057bf284b8,train,jane  fonda  –  julia  as  lillian  hellman , B-PER  I-PER  O  B-CW  O  B-PER  I-PER
9a908eb8-962c-4248-a3dd-1720b4666968,train,"on  the  first  episode  of  season  thirty  one  of  jeopardy!  ,  jeopardy  ! ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O
b5f465e7-a854-4dce-a027-dac0606e83c9,train,the  pair  also  run  a  separate  podcasting  channel  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O
ea916f1b-b9a5-4959-9537-aeb875c1faf1,train,"his  work  is  held  in  the  collections  of  the  j.  paul  getty  museum  ,  metropolitan  museum  of  art  ,  museum  of  fine  arts,  houston  ,  and  museum  of  modern  art  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O
8d7d50df-015d-43a7-ac46-8c1e9dfe465a,train,he  taught  this  line  of  work  at  the  accademia  albertina  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
5e1a950e-5a79-4603-868c-956730134f00,train,"after  a  long  break  ,  at  the  beginning  of  1996  ,  he  issued  naposletku...  (  after  all  .  .  .  )  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
2e92f2f2-fbed-4642-8029-b29c2669253e,train,"she  also  meets  two  versions  of  jesus  —  a  kindly  but  ineffective  young  man  ,  and  another  who  makes  a  living  by  posing  for  an  artist  depicting  him  on  a  cross  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
0862314b-1f83-42b4-8e09-078469e89a2c,train,bbc  radio  3  has  also  played  their  music  in  mainstream  programmes  . , B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
1d45d106-21e0-4da7-b53f-390cd644964d,train,the  first  type  was  built  by  hohenzollern  locomotive  works  and  baldwin  locomotive  works  in  1928  and  1929  respectively  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O
938a2a9b-0c8f-4b84-b4ed-e77ac56b8bb6,train,due  to  the  fact  that  there  are  two  different  materials  in  dfsw  ;  formation  of  a  composite  material  structure  within  the  nugget  zone  is  inevitable  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
ff5c5359-9ebf-445a-a4de-2e8d3abf85fb,train,the  club  is  a  member  of  the  galway  gaa  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
6cf512c6-8383-497f-8e6f-cb5563052883,train,one  of  his  doctoral  students  was  kazimierz  twardowski  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
1a875457-a8f3-41e3-ba17-5609e52425e2,train,"after  the  association  of  the  two  newspapers  ,  léon  nicole  served  as  their  editor  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O
0c13c99c-0ebc-48cd-a218-6014bd013c1f,train,"danses  concertantes  is  a  work  for  chamber  orchestra  by  igor  stravinsky  ,  composed  in  1942  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O
ef030a2a-93f9-4e09-8aed-e20d67d45bef,train,"jeanne  marni  (  1854  –  1910  ,  france  )  ,  nv  .  &  pw  . ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
d8e7dbc2-6002-452d-8a9e-ec17d6e6d955,train,"the  vendor  members  sell  street  food  or  other  goods  ,  such  as  fresh  flowers  and  toys  . ", O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
65fc8c67-3b31-4dee-b488-fb9c508111a3,train,he  played  in  major  league  baseball  (  mlb  )  for  the  baltimore  orioles  . , O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
5b551e08-be30-44d4-8c87-edff0daa4eb7,train,it  is  known  from  papua  new  guinea  . , O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O
a8677d9b-9fda-4fae-b3eb-e8bc292ec56c,train,odom  is  a  superfan  of  the  rock  band  night  ranger  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
cc14d714-ac17-4166-900d-501972fa4406,train,welenchiti  is  served  by  a  railway  station  on  the  addis  ababa–djibouti  railway  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O
4f9ac838-0e09-4d9c-b0dd-6a7c6c7dd9f8,train,the  main  works  were  at  irlam  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O
24130875-9e1b-4747-bba4-bd0e465e6739,train,"among  these  peoples  turquoise  was  used  in  mosaic  inlay  ,  in  sculptural  works  ,  and  was  fashioned  into  toroidal  beads  and  freeform  pendants  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
f60c4d0b-a721-422e-89ee-3fdfad20a69d,train,in  1990  italian  post  issued  a  stamp  in  his  honor  . , O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
850fb7b1-b5b3-4d12-875e-50ac6021de68,train,"approximately  2,169  developers  across  14  studios  worked  on  the  last  of  us  part  ii  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O
537d918b-82bd-4bf7-8a3e-fcc15eeaf5dc,train,"in  1613  ,  he  continued  his  education  at  university  of  basel  (  where  his  grandfather  had  also  studied  )  ,  in  geneva  and  sedan  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  B-LOC  O
2ab5e20b-f215-4df9-943c-fc3fa218761e,train,the  music  video  for  the  title  track  was  filmed  by  canon  inc.  as  a  campaign  for  their  4k  canon  eos  c500  camera  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  O  O
5ce3e012-ebc8-43cd-9767-3fca146fd9e4,train,"in  2017  ,  amy  chu  began  writing  the  series  . ", O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O
5c5f989a-1d79-4110-824f-b06250a5cb38,train,"guinness  world  records  2002  classified  it  as  the  most  valuable  tooth  ,  which  would  value  approximately  £  25,000  (  35,700  )  in  late  2001  . ", B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
34b0d123-d739-4e1f-aa98-be2a50e3b7f0,train,"the  show  makes  extensive  use  of  1980s  popular  music  ,  including  nena  99  luftballons  ,  david  bowie  ,  new  order  and  eurythmics  among  others  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  B-CW  I-CW  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  B-GRP  O  O  O
9d75d49d-33dc-4cb4-823b-1650448b33cf,train,it  fixed  some  bugs  and  added  support  for  half  height  floppy  drives  and  the  new  ibm  pcjr  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O
87695bf4-c9c0-49cb-89f5-826361e47fb3,train,"the  following  is  a  list  of  works  about  paris  ,  france  : ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  B-LOC  O
3267ff5d-d846-4bea-9267-ee1f123f6374,train,"parry  thomas  became  chief  engineer  at  leyland  motors  ,  a  company  whose  main  products  were  commercial  vehicles  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
ab968c63-faf3-462a-9a74-f89e2a284e45,train,"mongolia  has  an  embassy  in  tokyo  ,  established  in  1973  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O
4fd01ea5-2158-42be-a86b-e233bd9056f5,train,"comprising  several  municipalities  and  urban  centres  ,  the  subregion  's  capital  is  setúbal  ,  and  includes  several  cities  including  almada  and  setúbal  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  B-LOC  O
2a5bb14a-0e73-4c23-94e9-e62738457f73,train,"in  1923  ,  he  founded  the  organization  rodobrana  (  home  guard  )  ,  an  armed  militia  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
6153a171-b13b-43a5-a084-41fc9cf6cb41,train,"she  began  working  on  the  series  as  a  producer  and  screenwriter  in  2007  during  the  series  desperate  housewives,  season  4  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O
0b124490-8bc5-49d9-a375-7c945df621a8,train,"these  online  features  were  still  considered  a  breakthrough  in  video  games  ,  but  the  competing  playstation  2  did  not  ship  with  a  built  in  network  adapter  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
10c7c3f4-ddc6-4ecf-a647-9dc63786ae01,train,"built  in  germany  by  h.  c.  stülcken  sohn  at  steinwerder  ,  hamburg  . ", O  O  B-LOC  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  B-LOC  O  B-LOC  O
f4deffa4-234b-407c-83d3-497826365849,train,he  was  a  versatile  actor  who  could  handle  with  ease  the  hand  fan  used  by  poor  scholars  and  pheasant  plumes  worn  by  generals  on  their  helmets  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
f062f7a2-3ecd-4bb5-a809-3ed4bbcad802,train,"porkins  has  gained  some  comedic  notoriety  due  to  his  size  ,  manner  and  untimely  death  ,  which  was  spoofed  in  the  family  guy  episode  blue  harvest  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  B-CW  I-CW  O
0c5b827e-6d25-49af-bfa5-bac2b018e4e1,train,"during  his  childhood  ,  he  accompanied  his  father  to  meetings  of  alcoholics  anonymous  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
2e8d14a6-b106-4c62-8ae1-87b189de3d9b,train,"eulenhald  near  waldleiningen  ,  (  c  .  19  ha  )  , ", O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
27a7c297-3ca8-472a-ada1-0116af0e3c7c,train,"when  he  was  freed  ,  he  rushed  to  the  court  of  charles  v  of  france  to  renew  his  allegiance  and  rejoin  bertrand  du  guesclin  troops  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  O
36da1701-a5a7-4cbe-a707-5674221dcb5b,train,he  later  trained  under  then  consejo  mundial  de  lucha  libre  lead  trainer  el  satánico  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
09c67087-59a0-4a5b-8920-00ff43851d0d,train,character  has  an  unlockable  alternate  livery  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O
0f5ed288-100d-4469-ae67-d3b96d6b8967,train,runners  up  :  chocolat  •  france  and  camille  claudel  •  france , O  O  O  B-CW  O  B-LOC  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  B-LOC
8f2f886d-8122-4d34-b218-3addd496fd0c,train,it  's  also  seen  in  toy  story  2  and  a  trailer  for  toy  story  3 , O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW
73047169-cd55-4d66-ba03-9960767fe0df,train,"his  son  ,  shintarō  hirase  ,  (  1884  1939  )  was  also  a  malacologist  . ", O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
fd8a723e-5244-40de-bcc7-dc916a40f283,train,"malcolm  todd  ,  73  ,  historian  and  archaeologist  . ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
fc90e731-ede3-43b3-b30c-e414503ff9ff,train,"liu  wanting  sun  shengnan  6  –  7  (  1  –  7  )  ,  6  –  3  ,  [  10  –  7  ] ", B-PER  I-PER  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
e8f69c2a-17ea-495a-ab66-a0d5d550fb0f,train,"during  a  1981  annual  review  ,  he  uncovered  a  $  50  million  fraud  scheme  involving  ad  powerhouse  j.  walter  thompson  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O
6da2102d-41d0-402d-b71c-e63a2ad4318b,train,"while  auditioning  for  television  and  film  roles  ,  she  worked  on  theatre  productions  of  romeo  and  juliet  and  arsenic  and  old  lace  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O
593d5a1c-60f2-4736-a3c6-0b75cb48fa80,train,"the  road  fighting  championship  bantamweight  division  ,  with  upper  limit  at  135.6  lb  (  61.5  kg  ) ", O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
45632026-e303-46cd-a646-5a062e077990,train,eliot  graduated  from  the  yale  university  (  later  known  as  yale  college  )  in  1706  . , O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
07cd4ad0-97c2-45a9-9508-39afd68f6b84,train,it  was  the  world  's  first  computer  reservations  system  for  trains  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O
136bc35f-afcd-4072-bd77-21442cb28e38,train,"michel  sanchez  ,  who  was  member  of  the  band  deep  forest  ,  co  wrote  the  lyrics  . ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O
3d463405-50ea-4156-8467-4777acc8ec64,train,"his  last  theatrical  composition  was  music  for  joan  the  woman  ,  starring  geraldine  farrar  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
d25433c3-f46a-4b29-9da6-4760bf9f0738,train,"the  rest  of  the  beat  is  constructed  out  of  machine  gun  sprays  ,  nintendo  themes  and  bottle  blows  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O
989ea4e5-3418-48bc-b1b1-59669c0594ff,train,"vlade  divac  ,  basketball  player  ,  general  manager  of  the  sacramento  kings ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP
a088aec1-9824-4d3c-9a03-be02bed8d1b8,train,he  is  known  for  presenting  the  nos  journaal  from  1996  till  2009  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O
9d0b1490-3ef5-485e-be57-c5063ae99e43,train,she  started  her  career  as  a  consultant  with  pricewaterhousecoopers  in  kenya  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  B-LOC  O
7d865daf-d18b-4232-90ff-b1a309a4af51,train,"bygrave  lives  in  queenscliff  with  her  husband  ,  multi  award  winning  writer  and  poet  barry  hill  . ", O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
db34d60a-8bc3-47c3-bbc3-e287889f08e4,train,a  new  recording  of  this  work  was  made  in  1993  with  tom  waits  singing  along  with  the  original  recording  of  the  vagrant  during  the  final  section  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
961f7f66-8542-4f6c-80be-5b678a447c62,train,it  essentially  is  a  collarless  polo  shirt  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O
fdc5cb20-0076-4d0d-acd2-68782f6b1e36,train,"pragoti  is  the  state  run  automotive  industry  ,  which  assembles  mitsubishi  pajero  sport  ,  tata  motors  trucks  ,  and  ashok  leyland  minibus  . ", B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O
31fa054c-8474-4f75-bf60-609c38bb63d9,train,,
2efdebc2-4feb-4988-b717-f88b6c51c7f6,train,he  spent  the  1950  –  51  season  in  the  national  professional  basketball  league  (  npbl  )  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O
9eca1cb0-5714-4f89-ba72-5678d86ad6a9,train,"he  has  previously  worked  at  networks  including  channel  4  ,  itv  and  al  jazeera  english  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  B-CORP  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O
f57b0843-e6df-4fa4-87e7-e0d46207f12a,train,july  21  –  mos  burger  was  founded  . , O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O
b9799a06-3a97-46f6-99ca-b1ba7ac5a10c,train,mbali  ntuli  was  appointed  as  his  successor  . , B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O
5959ed1f-db8d-4739-9b11-d5faaaee343f,train,her  brother  was  the  conservative  party  politician  rab  butler  . , O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
81cb2eb4-877d-418b-a3b0-b6c620a04568,train,cross  with  nail  in  evros  regional  unit  /  greece  ]  ] , O  O  B-PROD  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O
1cdcda17-fe18-425f-90b7-e2c54f43c4f1,train,"he  served  as  the  head  football  coach  at  allegheny  college  from  2002  to  2015  ,  compiling  a  record  of  62  –  79  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
cb774320-15fa-4e47-a098-afae86759119,train,"røyken  videregående  skole  is  an  unesco  aspnet  school  ,  and  offers  several  international  exchange  programs  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
fcd6b511-ef63-4459-8670-21a9ebd3a144,train,the  video  was  a  10  minute  long  short  film  and  gathered  an  audience  of  400  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
3dbc02af-6a4e-4fb7-9017-71c4a848452b,train,"the  book  received  praise  from  the  economist  ,  the  guardian  ,  and  bill  gates  ,  who  called  it  one  of  the  best  books  on  energy  that  has  been  written  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
a59d45ab-71db-4def-a0d8-a7e7873825be,train,"she  recorded  jingles  for  major  companies  such  as  toyota  ,  american  airlines  ,  and  max  factor  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
6ade758e-0649-4229-8496-4c216bec4cd2,train,the  game  is  based  upon  the  fantasy  novels  nine  princes  in  amber  (  doubleday  1970  )  and  the  guns  of  avalon  (  doubleday  1972  )  by  roger  zelazny  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  B-CORP  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
fe8c948d-e24a-47f7-a924-4f421959fb08,train,"the  series  also  produced  spin  off  titles  including  saga  and  mana  ,  and  in  turn  influenced  later  game  developers  and  studios  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
e9ef13bc-ba67-42a4-bb08-68670e8d671b,train,"in  the  hbo  game  of  thrones  ,  he  is  portrayed  by  charles  dance  . ", O  O  B-CORP  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
3c455b11-6163-488b-a02b-f6381af61082,train,a  popular  use  is  rendering  an  animated  3d  scene  as  an  adobe  flash  file  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O
bd3005f5-9e00-42e6-816d-6e1c42885f5c,train,he  also  opened  a  studio  on  the  isle  of  man  where  he  spent  his  summers  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O
070b6ced-2f6d-48cb-94c5-e54fe8972ba4,train,the  album  was  released  in  1990  by  sparrow  records  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
a1ae6fba-7548-4215-bdd8-7ea9ec96fbd4,train,"postman  pat  (  1981  ,  1991  –  1994  ,  1996  ,  2004  –  2008  ) ", B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
86cb2d58-c36f-445f-b0c7-48497e5cfede,train,he  stayed  in  leipzig  in  1768  and  hamburg  in  1769  . , O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O
6fcbddb6-19a5-49a0-8821-121c0c9e0591,train,"in  more  recent  years  ,  he  has  served  on  the  boards  of  media  companies  such  as  cbs  and  chicago  tribune  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
6a7722a5-32c1-49b8-9b14-322c13d5fd28,train,"aerogel  has  the  density  of  glass  ,  another  silicon  based  solid  to  which  it  may  be  compared  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
8cddaeb6-8dc1-4a54-8e06-f482d53afa0f,train,the  film  had  musical  score  by  b.  a.  chidambaranath  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O
eef9b527-a91b-4794-b089-e6acaaf91db2,train,her  mother  was  an  opera  singer  and  her  father  worked  in  the  textile  industry  . , O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
6fa84cfb-1750-4649-9950-27ca0981c1a3,train,"pinky  wore  the  same  outfit  as  in  her  happy  days  episodes  ,  though  her  hair  was  now  in  a  70s  style  shag  cut  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
ed3608fe-3290-4ca2-8b06-42bab5532f12,train,iron  sky  and  nazis  at  the  center  of  the  earth  (  both  released  in  2012  )  are  in  a  similar  vein  . , B-CW  I-CW  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
fa1ac13b-553d-43cb-9a71-f74a58f90afa,train,"they  were  extensively  refurbished  between  1989  and  1992  by  eastleigh  works  ,  for  use  on  services  on  the  isle  of  wight  island  line,  isle  of  wight  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O
5c8f61b7-d034-450e-bf83-c6d6a2870aaa,train,"ac  propulsion  ebox  ,  a  type  of  automobile ", B-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O
68dd3974-888a-4aa9-86d8-9636fed53367,train,a  2014  rolling  stone  reader  's  poll  ranked  it  the  group  's  fourth  best  song  . , O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
75981173-f61e-448c-ab32-4508ccd13f33,train,"mos  def  ,  talib  kweli  ,  that  whole  rawkus  records  scene  ,  that  's  my  type  of  shit  . ", B-PER  I-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
1e79e60c-4d83-4e86-a520-7fd71bd226f6,train,the  philippine  daily  inquirer  is  founded  and  publishes  its  first  issue  . , O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
9a083801-8c37-4fd0-804e-98c7cf239d65,train,"the  hollywood  reporter  estimated  the  film  lost  the  studio  around  $  70  million  ,  when  factoring  together  all  expenses  and  revenues  . ", B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
a6bca4ce-bb6b-4098-b859-960ace1675fc,train,the  film  is  available  for  free  at  the  website  of  the  national  library  of  norway  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O
c0ed3198-8342-49c4-8c7a-be4bef52ead3,train,"he  conducted  two  albums  ,  both  for  decca  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O
1fdfb9bc-63ee-494e-8c2f-cedb0dca558b,train,tesla  .  (  defunct  ;  was  active  in  the  1980s  and  1990s  ) , B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
cbb9b5b6-49cd-40d1-b4a7-e3f208e50bda,train,"brian  j.  smith  (  born  1981  )  ,  actor  ,  stargate  universe  ,  sense8 ", B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  B-CW
3de4e94a-3195-429c-a57d-76f9c11e9b2e,train,during  the  reign  of  ibn  saud  he  was  the  most  significant  non  royal  official  . , O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
1b5a26ba-0713-4c2c-8fe5-9c141ebdf789,train,"tithes  )  is  the  seventh  tractate  of  zeraim  (  order  of  seeds  )  of  the  mishnah  ,  tosefta  ,  and  the  jerusalem  talmud  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  B-CW  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O
845494f9-71f0-4102-8ad2-fc1ad1033b68,train,"de3  –  0-4-0  ,  400  hp  ,  50  tons  ,  25  mph ", O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
02f5b1e6-8bf3-4be3-937e-d989f8f82c4e,train,"it  is  located  north  of  elgin  and  about  south  of  the  washington  border  ,  at  an  elevation  of  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
0958d6cc-d56d-45c9-99dc-75c80be56f2b,train,the  main  river  in  the  district  is  the  saale  with  wine  along  the  river  valley  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O
971d32c7-2dc7-4fb1-be3b-dcb4005661f4,train,the  western  canada  hockey  league  was  the  first  major  professional  league  on  the  prairies  . , O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
e646f569-5338-4a88-9cbb-1cf602f7c25e,train,harvey  brooks  –  bass  guitar  (  highway  61  revisited  ) , B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
0bc2373e-ee08-492a-8655-2c96814f6235,train,"established  in  1972  ,  the  pakistan  naval  air  arm  provides  fleet  air  defence  ,  maritime  reconnaissance  ,  and  anti  submarine  warfare  capability  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
75c5c94c-af6b-46ee-b128-a62515f74be6,train,one  was  intercepted  by  iron  dome  ;  the  other  fell  in  an  open  area  near  the  city  . , O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
d529ab83-7adf-4f08-ad68-6b98e4815974,train,he  also  appeared  in  the  film  crossroads  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O
2fbc9514-6819-45a6-9841-6dadf87f9015,train,he  was  included  in  the  list  of  100  most  influential  indian  by  the  indian  express  and  also  named  journalist  of  the  year  by  mumbai  press  club  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
110d4745-f762-4e95-b353-fa92c41fba84,train,"for  example  ,  typical  fresh  chili  peppers  have  a  water  content  around  90  %  ,  whereas  tabasco  sauce  has  a  water  content  of  95  %  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
eb0273dd-2880-497a-80de-b0cfe9865345,train,it  is  the  fourth  single  from  the  former  duo  's  first  extended  play  bouquet  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  B-CW  O
d0788d3e-c179-433f-b049-d510935260d6,train,alexander  is  credited  with  laying  the  foundations  of  music  education  in  the  dallas  public  schools  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O
c9d5d127-4363-4e3d-b370-619fb334969b,train,"cooktop  ,  the  top  cooking  surface  on  a  kitchen  stove ", B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD
e58b573f-5064-4bf7-9b82-97371d72a772,train,"galindians  were  two  distinct  ,  and  now  extinct  ,  tribes  of  the  balts  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  O
92d2f1a3-f71c-4206-a4db-b9b751555cec,train,sp  3606  is  privately  owned  as  part  of  a  collection  of  former  railroad  cars  in  rocklin  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O
410ccd59-8b41-47e9-a640-11cb919b7541,train,made  part  of  the  jilin–shulan  railway  in  1941 , O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  O
c1c3b3a1-e08b-4290-8953-fd051e624a34,train,"in  1485  ,  the  area  was  included  to  the  grand  duchy  of  moscow  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O
1d035ec5-a647-4c61-8a42-4d0d2fc53e58,train,"he  then  spent  8  seasons  with  fc  volendam  ,  for  whom  he  scored  48  goals  in  218  games  in  all  competitions  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
155f5c33-f9b1-4331-96f5-f9a27300dc84,train,he  was  a  member  of  the  federalist  party  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
ba97741c-20ab-4300-8523-2466b239c00e,train,"renninger  considered  the  game  too  easy  ,  and  believed  that  the  links  was  superior  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O
5f9de98a-088b-4cf3-afee-c00f204a8802,train,senegal  has  also  seen  an  increase  in  life  expectancy  at  birth  from  57  %  in  2000  to  67.38  %  in  2017  . , B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
f103cd1b-67a2-4144-8e8f-d0be85463cc4,train,"president  in  :  hot  shots!  part  deux  (  film  ,  1993  ) ", O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O
83529579-3cdc-498a-960b-68691ee8891a,train,randolph  was  born  in  nashville  . , O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O
c20e4ee8-9188-48cf-8cdd-e9d9b08697b4,train,"during  his  nine  year  professional  career  ,  he  appeared  almost  exclusively  for  local  s.c.  braga  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
2af0253d-fac7-43c4-8274-2cc6347a2954,train,"tex  beneke  (  1914  –  2000  )  ,  big  band  saxophonist  ,  singer  ,  bandleader ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
645b212e-eeac-470e-a312-cac7d1357ac9,train,hymn  to  germany  for  medium  voice  and  piano  ;  words  by  rudolf  alexander  schröder , B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER
23318259-66b0-4d0b-a9a5-00400496f623,train,uk  :  leicester  :  mini  excavators  ;  peterlee  :  articulated  dump  trucks  ;  peterborough  :  engines  ;  larne  and  belfast  :  generating  sets  . , O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O
743ff7d7-6678-46de-8b47-b26d88e13a3a,train,u.s.  swimmer  scott  weltz  finished  fifth  in  2  :  09.02  to  hold  off  his  teammate  clark  burckle  (  2  :  09.25  )  by  23  hundredths  of  a  second  . , O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
c4f4bbb6-1219-44fb-a7fa-32c1bef168ae,train,"similar  to  many  other  forms  of  divination  ,  the  diviner  casts  table  salt  crystals  into  the  air  and  interprets  the  patterns  as  it  falls  to  the  ground  or  travels  through  the  air  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
5c950575-739b-4a0a-bf07-a27f13be2eef,train,"the  main  campus  of  mountains  of  the  moon  university  ,  a  private  university  ,  is  located  in  the  city  center  . ", O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
377afdb4-e9ee-434a-9ce8-382b02b1be5f,train,the  movie  was  reported  to  be  inspired  by  sholay  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O
9523ef45-4c9e-45fe-a6c4-ca89e7c32a8a,train,blanchard  scored  his  first  goal  for  the  club  in  a  1  –  1  draw  with  crawley  town  f.c.  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O
fa4f252a-ac11-44bd-a311-519352c9189c,train,;  voiced  by  brenda  vaccaro  in  season  1  ;  rhea  perlman  in  season  2 , O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O
6813d769-9415-42e8-a8c6-fcdfc16ee78b,train,"andrew  has  also  been  a  member  of  the  dallas  cowboys  ,  new  york  jets  ,  philadelphia  eagles  ,  and  minnesota  vikings  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
24839afc-8e5e-45fd-8554-b209ac71094b,train,"in  1979  ,  under  her  direction  ,  a  documentary  about  simone  de  beauvoir  appeared  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  O
c61e010d-a316-45c7-b82a-d7af321b9ed6,train,"the  rolling  chassis  is  delivered  to  the  commercial  body  maker  ,  coachbuilder  ,  or  bulk  transporter  on  its  own  wheels  ,  under  its  own  power  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
2f4ed29c-69dd-4cf1-b7d1-022b9fcbffc5,train,"emi  ,  a  music  and  electronics  group  of  companies ", B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
359cfeab-fcc0-4fbb-828c-9e48550bde42,train,it  is  located  in  the  municipality  of  rakovica  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O
c60699fd-c73a-42d1-886b-895080a65e45,train,coffee  would  be  included  in  the  same  manner  . , B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
252fbc63-5ac5-430b-b6ee-e697b7dfa5c0,train,it  was  released  in  1969  on  atlantic  records  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
e60ef70e-778b-4c31-a189-6db58ca1c9b0,train,"joseph  whitworth  devised  a  series  of  standards  for  engineering  ,  and  built  a  rifle  with  an  accurately  rifled  barrel  . ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
ac192718-e49d-4b0e-9d4f-8d81cd76ff51,train,"the  third  ,  scherzo  like  movement  ,  has  an  easy  spirit  yet  is  full  of  complex  rhythms  and  interwoven  textures  . ", O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
eea75781-525b-4677-b046-5341c3d1e044,train,a  zoetrope  is  a  device  used  for  animation  . , O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
698aaac2-19f5-404f-9ba1-9ce3e849bb12,train,"he  published  first  illustration  in  lui  ,  l'expansion  and  cosmopolitan  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  B-CW  O  B-CW  O
a79b1571-0dce-4a33-8cd4-2b71ef01bac1,train,"a  saddle  chair  encourages  this  natural  posture  ,  which  is  the  same  as  when  lying  on  the  side  while  sleeping  . ", O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
52179eae-e92d-4054-a2e4-8c7bb79b0269,train,the  demo  was  later  released  on  the  quadrophenia  box  set  of  2011  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O
1da7f478-d62e-4b65-9b7c-01ecd3b52c7e,train,former  professional  football  player  for  the  new  york  jets , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP
d043feb4-46e0-41e6-8953-aac01de8367c,train,"more  recently  ,  the  church  has  faced  an  increased  demand  for  suburb  and  a  decline  in  attendance  to  inner  city  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O
6ebed57b-8bce-47b1-97c2-d4dd0cf047f3,train,ocean  city  retains  its  ban  but  exempts  persons  with  a  concealed  weapons  permit  from  the  ban  . , B-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
ce106989-6093-4683-ab9b-e1a979ae654a,train,the  book  's  sometimes  cynical  humor  has  been  described  as  similar  to  the  onion  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
f3d6d099-5c5b-4246-b27e-d828e5503f85,train,"tremonti  ,  a  solo  project  by  the  above  musician ", B-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
b5b9abef-edf0-4a3c-9e43-dac89423c29c,train,"since  2008  ,  he  has  been  the  senior  vice  president  of  disney  television  animation  (  owned  by  the  walt  disney  company  )  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O
08421dc6-8af7-488a-b6bc-8f239b6ea9ff,train,the  song  featured  chris  trousdale  from  dream  street  and  received  high  rotation  on  radio  disney  . , O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
f02d29f2-46aa-4c65-a4eb-bd1b98cb568e,train,"nostradameus  (  paul  rugg  )  claims  to  be  able  to  predictiate  the  future  ,  though  he  is  proven  wrong  on  occasion  . ", B-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
867d142e-fda6-4eb0-92a8-2e12d255d28f,train,a  statue  of  benjamin  franklin  was  displayed  at  the  entrance  . , O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O
0ac6aa66-2e64-4d7a-beb9-f24618bf25a3,train,rolls  collected  art  including  sketches  by  henry  fuseli  and  illuminated  manuscripts  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O
6e4e2a4e-4aea-44d6-af9d-3869be324f65,train,"jorge  martínez  de  hoyos  (  el  abuelo  y  yo  ,  1993  )  and  ignacio  lópez  tarso  (  de  pocas,  pocas  pulgas  ,  2003  ) ", B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O
d7ec4602-e4bd-426a-b970-920b5e637d9d,train,it  became  widely  ridiculed  on  the  soup  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O
b6a7a0cd-614f-42c0-bb95-658d5495d926,train,"in  1941  she  was  appointed  to  the  staff  of  the  royal  academy  of  music  where  ,  starting  with  seven  students  ,  she  built  the  drama  course  to  70  students  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
b17fd0e0-2c87-41eb-9543-e7430d1f2fd0,train,"fantasea  ,  a  1978  surf  movie  with  shaun  tomson ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER
49cf0500-b155-4ee6-9cc1-154d1ebc3d0f,train,he  also  served  as  a  fundraiser  and  consultant  for  the  democratic  national  committee  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O
e10a5e32-bbe1-4401-9670-865bcc297843,train,top  4  :  don't  stop  me  now  queen  (  pop  jazz  ;  choreographer  :  tba  ) , O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  B-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
b432033d-292d-4665-8c37-bfe1501cf9fb,train,"celebration  is  a  compilation  album  by  switzerland  singer  dj  bobo  ,  released  in  2002  . ", O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  B-LOC  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O
25ef42ad-43f9-4f7a-b343-31965180cab6,train,karta  bink  was  born  in  commewijne  district  in  about  1972  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O
4be4651d-a098-4583-97d1-57ce39911e5e,train,"however  ,  the  party  began  to  move  away  from  revolutionary  socialism  at  the  turn  of  the  20th  century  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
ee86c829-e6f3-488c-bb7e-5c4f2f5a8cb5,train,hanriot  h  .  230  was  a  france  twin  engined  advanced  trainer  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O
7a447fbb-9038-4883-bbdc-e7a8c7d33a27,train,"mailen  auroux  maría  irigoyen  6  –  1  ,  2  –  6  ,  [  10  –  5  ] ", B-PER  I-PER  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
8e90915c-7a21-453d-b182-26f9aad8102d,train,the  great  western  highway  and  the  railway  defined  the  northern  limit  . , O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
5b308395-7a2a-4be4-81ad-9f9aedfdd2f6,train,"john  patterson  ,  former  pitcher  for  the  arizona  diamondbacks  . ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
0c4da2da-64cc-4e03-91fb-5503c788f6fe,train,"they  also  manufacture  electronic  carillons  ,  street  clock  ,  glockenspiels  ,  and  monuments  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O
165110aa-ed87-4d14-be74-ed8e4cb69cfd,train,the  product  range  includes  bag  and  suitcase  . , O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  B-PROD  O
bf220c75-763f-4975-aa43-12ebb8202d21,train,its  design  is  based  on  the  209  series  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O
b7c6fdbb-ee47-4a50-af50-2deb399fd465,train,"its  northern  border  follows  interstate  81  ,  and  its  eastern  border  follows  pennsylvania  route  39  . ", O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O
ae6bbf02-5db7-4226-94c8-963952d4a836,train,father  émile  petitot  describes  his  reception  in  1862  . , O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O
20b0f3e2-294d-44b0-85cb-5bfd16fd9c6a,train,"c  37b  or  gulfstream  g550  ,  a  business  jet ", O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O
cec12228-24a1-466b-a9cf-17c17d052ad1,train,"file  :  sauna  stove  narvi  02  .  jpg  |  wood  burning  sauna  stove  ,  finland ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  B-LOC
c1e1d04c-03eb-4c15-aa2d-8e1a4273be67,train,"capcom  purchased  the  intellectual  property  in  2012  and  provided  funding  for  the  project  ,  reimagining  it  as  an  action-adventure  game  for  release  on  multiple  platforms  . ", B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O
ce5fb3e1-0ace-4650-8a47-13a7fe851491,train,"in  1985  ,  he  tried  a  comeback  with  blue  bulls  ,  but  only  played  in  three  provincial  matches  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
c322968a-1061-4244-b751-4c84ee3dce55,train,this  chiefly  consisted  of  coal  in  the  area  north  of  llanelli  and  around  saundersfoot  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  B-LOC  O
eeba9db6-b08f-44aa-837e-1ff7462b9b7a,train,they  currently  play  in  the  macedonian  first  league  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O
b99cffdd-988b-4faf-a0a4-cbd51fceaa84,train,"he  finished  third  ,  behind  liberal  party  of  canada  nancy  karetak-lindell  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  B-PER  I-PER  O
dbfceb6e-7926-4191-9dfa-ac2ebb376e5d,train,"(  cannata  stayed  until  1981  ,  returning  for  the  river  of  dreams  recording  sessions  in  1993  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O
aa5c8bac-7d7b-4123-9f50-e9a2912bd07b,train,it  is  a  neighbor  to  high  carihuairazo  volcano  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O
d31debd9-130b-46dc-92e4-06fcb9623ed8,train,"the  keypad  lock  feature  found  on  most  mobile  phones  is  intended  to  help  prevent  accidental  dialing  ,  but  is  often  so  trivial  that  the  keypad  is  easily  pocket  unlocked  . ", O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
f2c98dd8-3d83-4021-b025-426a6cd4e39e,train,it  was  even  featured  in  the  irish  independent  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
ce468751-ae41-4140-8c2a-87fc244352a3,train,"hershey  bar  ,  their  most  iconic  product ", B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O
32b0a202-7178-4e70-8250-5e4ccd364027,train,c’  est  ma  fête  –  it's  my  party , O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW
b821d46e-acd6-4839-93d9-49887cdf6701,train,in  2015  the  team  switched  from  ktm  to  husqvarna  motorcycles  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
e0da21e6-6ec8-4092-a6fa-64b4a73639a6,train,evelyn  keyes  in  a  bit  part  (  uncredited  ) , B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
4cc312c1-4f9d-4dbb-b06a-ea4c01204aeb,train,"she  attended  public  schools  in  worcester  ,  and  went  on  to  attend  wellesley  college  in  1902  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O
06239085-1c99-4c89-94a7-53ed6e6c1bf5,train,"in  1988  ,  it  was  adapted  into  a  funny  farm  ,  starring  chevy  chase  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
1bbc03a2-1382-41bc-a929-f9724a4fd46c,train,its  basement  hosts  kitchen  facilities  while  in  the  ground  floor  is  located  an  internet  café  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
39b7ee5d-0936-48e8-8ff0-9b0748ae9dff,train,"victor  svendsen  11  –  7  ,  11  –  7  ,  8  –  11  ,  10  –  12  ,  11  –  4 ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
655df740-053b-4c66-a8b5-04303d7659d7,train,sky  leads  the  cubs  to  the  mudflats  to  dig  up  clam  hiding  under  the  mud  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O
44614a07-196c-429d-a843-3ed6b065bed8,train,indian  locomotive  class  wap-7  locomotive  powers  the  train  end  to  end  . , B-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
26c96035-8464-4894-b782-2a2d1628ee09,train,he  made  his  debut  for  sogndal  fotball  in  a  1  1  draw  against  ik  start  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
76a1702d-fc9a-48ee-8d86-7e17b2c9e9c2,train,weight  tax  deduction  for  plug-in  hybrid  introduced , O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O
e05c59d6-6895-44ee-9cba-23d356a72a81,train,"for  maximum  flavor  and  aroma  ,  as  in  mulled  wine  ,  zest  is  simply  cut  from  the  fruit  with  a  knife  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
096c6717-1111-432a-a3e3-a7cfe95f97d5,train,remains  of  copper  smelting  sites  and  open  air  copper  mines  were  investigated  in  1984  –  1985  . , O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
3cffa39f-ae38-45cd-bb9f-a9c74b331a0e,train,"after  the  film  's  release  ,  the  song  became  a  hit  and  a  jazz  standard  ,  and  has  been  widely  covered  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
9c6d319a-4230-4064-acf2-1491cba9cb13,train,the  airport  is  a  hub  for  both  united  airlines  and  frontier  airlines  and  a  base  for  southwest  airlines  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
853f0aeb-6a8a-40bd-b827-d7ca5920e1e2,train,"a  few  days  later  ,  harry  houdini  comes  to  town  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O
6f5968dd-bf70-425f-b19f-8224868b13cd,train,"according  to  his  employment  record  ,  he  worked  as  a  loader  for  the  united  parcel  service  from  1983  to  1997  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O
3df8ae58-ab37-49c2-b4df-e8d1755d282a,train,"the  album  features  six  different  covers  ,  depicting  each  of  the  various  band  members  death  mask  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O
8132d76d-f3e1-408a-aafc-741abcf3686b,train,"in  2012  ,  the  chevrolet  cobalt  was  added  to  the  production  line  . ", O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
c35465ac-bb08-4dda-96a2-b2da8f9892ae,train,"goya  learned  from  these  sources  ,  and  from  rembrandt  ,  some  of  whose  prints  he  owned  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
2a37364b-b17b-411a-88b6-641b43de5ec0,train,from  1962  to  1965  he  was  ambassador  in  bonn  (  germany  ) , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  B-LOC  O
9cc468d1-0936-4ab6-9ce1-e7b62dc66652,train,"in  2017  ,  he  moved  to  helsingin  jalkapalloklubi  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O
7b50790d-d0b7-4451-82fe-872b7dfb5860,train,"torchlight  iii  ,  a  2020  action  role  playing  game ", B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
c227982a-7dc9-4d5f-87dd-2524d246ebd4,train,it  stars  shaina  magdayao  in  the  title  role  . , O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O
b373e9e8-a264-4ac8-a3bd-6330c062a9ff,train,"as  for  wheat  ,  another  staple  ,  it  took  another  three  or  four  thousand  years  . ", O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
e4a1a9c6-64ea-4c40-9663-8fe38789c065,train,he  moved  to  peru  for  eight  years  . , O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O
1339ff53-fdd0-4c3f-a812-95af8dfc0fdb,train,"deutch  was  born  in  los  angeles  ,  california  ,  to  actress  lea  thompson  and  director  howard  deutch  . ", O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
c5fa941d-87a1-4632-9f4d-ce41aff19ed3,train,"ferdinand  ,  the  main  character  of  the  story  of  ferdinand ", O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW
5e05617c-f266-4779-be8a-558b7cce63f6,train,"in  1997  ,  bbc  radio  4  broadcast  a  dramatization  of  the  story  in  six  half  hour  episodes  ,  later  re  edited  into  three  hour  long  episodes  . ", O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
6d075e28-2bfe-42c3-929f-a27de694a242,train,"lau  would  later  turn  down  the  role  ,  and  wang  xueqi  was  cast  instead  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O
00f3ff5c-ef9a-4798-ae0a-fd571d83291b,train,"he  moved  to  stockport  county  f.c.  ,  playing  50  times  before  joining  tranmere  rovers  f.c.  . ", O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O
17c69c91-b92b-46e1-9f80-70aa894cde7a,train,"it  is  the  first  major  white  rap  record  ,  predating  the  recording  of  blondie  rapture  by  six  months  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  B-CW  O  O  O  O
8c41b541-93f5-4da4-90e5-d26504543ded,train,"it  was  rebuilt  by  benjamin  ferrey  in  1856  ,  on  the  site  of  an  earlier  church  ,  but  closed  in  1970  . ", O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
14cb4331-7a77-4b93-b46d-9d247c94b8b3,train,"horatio  allen  ,  designed  world  's  first  articulated  locomotive  in  1832 ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O
d8189208-9e60-4c96-9c4e-116baac7028f,train,"for  the  following  year  a  new  car  ,  the  ferrari  412  t2  came  out  which  received  many  changes  that  aided  both  aero  and  safety  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
16b969a9-52cd-45c0-b845-b32691ad1896,train,"it  was  sung  then  by  john  henry  johnstone  ,  and  it  was  later  a  favourite  piece  of  charles  incledon  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
bd5aa3f7-90e7-4c70-8aa7-794f90d49407,train,he  played  for  the  miami  dolphins  in  1966  . , O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O
7165fd73-5297-46ea-8601-0163ff4ef1e9,train,ensenada  is  where  the  fender  musical  instruments  corporation  standard  series  guitars  and  basses  are  produced  . , O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
a7d5c593-a910-47de-a6c9-2c8da461c10f,train,"sugar  sprinkled  on  cut  fruit  will  draw  out  the  water  through  hydrophilia  ,  making  the  fruit  mushy  and  wet  ,  as  in  a  common  strawberry  compote  recipe  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O
b4537491-11f5-490a-9acf-d43aa10de8b9,train,shocking  blue  at  home  including  venus , B-GRP  I-GRP  B-CW  I-CW  O  B-CW
19184d64-c797-45cd-a414-5489eccc3714,train,"the  ant  and  the  aardvark  ,  a  cartoon  series  that  inspired  the  game  . ", B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
340ade13-d7c0-42fd-9cb6-4066d1b8f8f0,train,"the  south  gallery  was  extended  to  the  east  end  and  the  pulpit  ,  by  then  three  decker  ,  was  relocated  to  the  centre  of  the  nave  aisle  at  the  east  end  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
3a681027-b539-4193-9a3b-7c54fb73da84,train,she  was  the  chairman  of  the  standing  commission  on  the  history  of  cartography  of  the  international  cartographic  association  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O
dd27a059-524a-4822-b533-e3fadbf89bb7,train,two  of  the  awards  go  to  lundgaard  &  tranberg  and  one  goes  to  3xn  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O
9ca63b66-d96b-4332-891e-920bdb26ed32,train,,
e2bab9b4-956b-4d94-97a3-53d559b54e60,train,a  force  play  provided  the  second  out  of  the  inning  but  boog  powell  single  drove  in  one  run  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O
627ac041-2ca0-47c1-bb08-c47c454fc8f1,train,"in  2010  ,  sony  pictures  television  ,  the  show  's  production  company  ,  released  an  adaptation  for  the  iphone  ,  ipod  touch  ,  and  ipad  . ", O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  B-PROD  O
3842bf39-0f4d-4e60-aae0-c56a91a8f140,train,,
7863296d-4d36-4fcd-8225-5854f8d4f761,train,"starring  bing  crosby  and  dorothy  lamour  ,  it  is  a  musical  film  directed  by  a.  edward  sutherland  . ", O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O
d02a5b5e-eb04-4628-b786-268ec6c1f7d1,train,"during  his  years  playing  the  nightclub  circuit  ,  he  met  and  became  friends  with  future  barney  miller  producer  danny  arnold  ,  who  was  also  a  performer  at  the  time  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
40a67b4b-b970-4a10-af5c-6184d83d988b,train,"it  is  owned  and  operated  by  tüpraş  ,  the  country  's  only  oil  refiner  with  four  refineries  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
4a09fe72-1092-46a5-918b-2ca313d7c9df,train,"the  hotel  features  121  bedrooms  and  suites  ,  spread  over  the  beach  front  resort  ,  and  16  andalusia  style  villas  throughout  of  gardens  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O
5c53cd9d-783c-4ea3-8505-397ee259292a,train,jwpce  can  also  display  kanji  in  a  list  you  generate  in  a  different  color  so  that  it  colors  either  the  kanji  that  the  user  does  not  know  or  that  the  user  does  know  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
4af5d909-437d-44c5-aee8-ea3b22e3275d,train,"a  recipe  is  a  set  of  instructions  that  describes  how  to  prepare  or  make  something  ,  especially  a  dish  of  prepared  food  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O
f479a14a-b84a-48ed-8671-345256e78176,train,"liverpool  also  suffered  severely  ,  with  many  shipwrecks  and  structural  damage  resulting  from  strong  winds  .  120  people  died  as  a  result  of  such  accidents  in  the  city  alone  . ", B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
61fcfa11-5715-4879-9994-2ad340e5a897,train,,
25014a4b-ffaf-402b-a245-115f60b15cbc,train,colecovision  's  main  competitor  was  the  less  commercially  successful  atari  5200  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O
cff47373-fffd-46bd-be01-70a28bbcd868,train,the  name  was  not  used  for  several  years  before  being  reused  for  the  ibm  pc  series  in  the  90s  and  early  2000s  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
764494b3-ed9c-48ab-91b4-f192bd5aa977,train,"apple  's  second  album  ,  when  the  pawn...  ,  was  released  in  1999  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O
99d52e7f-6f74-48ec-af80-94bcb582a8e2,train,"it  has  an  improved  camera  and  lens  ,  an  improved  screen  ,  battery  and  improved  interface  than  previous  model  samsung  s5560  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O
1c488183-dce7-4600-991e-4f294ecc1ff1,train,he  was  a  founding  member  of  the  société  française  de  photographie  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O
d035f0fa-f324-4880-9f9d-cadb8db1ed31,train,"taylor  's  second  film  of  1950  was  the  comedy  the  big  hangover  ,  co  starring  van  johnson  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
3b9e6a75-8d87-4f2a-b508-3d1104df5691,train,the  mantua  or  manteau  was  a  new  fashion  that  arose  in  the  1680s  . , O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
69e046b9-ca2a-4b03-a464-c105a747d287,train,he  currently  plays  for  sarmiento  de  junín  . , O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O
c8881868-33fd-497c-9946-26ef0a93de06,train,"the  structure  was  built  of  steel  ,  reinforced  concrete  ,  and  brick  ,  with  a  handsomely  designed  ivory  colored  terracotta  front  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O
958ca685-15ba-4458-8020-13f1e65cbc51,train,its  first  charter  also  dates  from  this  time  . , O  O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O
b1118a1c-86c0-4248-8180-fd35d4bbc43a,train,"special  appearances  as  customer  by  brian  joo  (  fly  to  the  sky  )  ,  heize  . ", O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  B-PER  O
89ae92c9-39c1-49b2-b06e-1eb69144ba49,train,"the  top  goalscorer  was  craig  brewster  ,  who  finished  the  season  with  20  goals  . ", O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
fa91faa4-45de-49a0-933e-ec2d326ba910,train,it  was  released  on  harvest  /  emi  as  a  single  in  1988  . , O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O
87364fea-2d83-4b05-948c-461abf73ba0d,train,it  was  later  the  home  field  of  the  calgary  vipers  baseball  team  of  the  north  american  league  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O
73def98e-4496-49f3-bbaf-f00fa1087b3e,train,they  each  got  a  sandpit  and  a  vacuum  cleaner  each  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O
4853fd14-e71d-43db-93d6-a8fe60a96fe3,train,rodriguez  appeared  in  the  abs-cbn  corporation  hit  drama  series  angelito:  batang  ama  as  a  regular  . , O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O
d1028f13-4257-4fb0-9b42-715171a8852f,train,jagertee  (  also  jägertee  )  is  an  alcoholic  punch  historically  made  by  mixing  stroh  with  spiced  black  tea  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O
5a598be3-0a28-40a1-bcfa-c6f3c7a99fdd,train,"the  lead  single  ,  la  puerta  del  cielo  /  seven  lives  ,  is  a  fusion  of  modern  and  classical  elements  . ", O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
5adac88f-0544-4c7f-970f-b13fc9411471,train,"kate  markowitz  harmony  vocals  (  1  ,  4  )  ,  background  vocals ", B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
3a72cef4-c23a-452d-97a8-5c0026886e17,train,young  has  stated  in  concert  that  he  wrote  the  song  while  studying  history  in  high  school  in  winnipeg  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O
d520bc8c-927a-4e93-8fca-c934cce7f242,train,"an  idealistic  young  priest  arrives  at  ambricourt  ,  his  new  parish  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O
9cec4743-3d14-43cc-b9e1-08c9217329d4,train,it  is  also  used  as  food  or  a  garnish  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O
86da8411-d153-445e-b4fc-0f02ca74d692,train,the  programme  attracted  high  ratings  for  the  then  new  channel  4  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
99f40c87-0ddd-4617-980a-cb88ce0162a2,train,opening  theme  song  for  masamune-kun's  revenge , O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW
a71eee11-766f-4faa-9308-cd22bbbd75b3,train,it  was  named  best  sports  film  of  all  time  by  usa  today  and  by  espn  expert  panel  and  website  users  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O
fc55c04d-d94a-431a-b094-bff67d7aac94,train,the  lifeboat  was  built  in  1923  by  j.  samuel  white  at  cowes  on  the  isle  of  wight  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  B-LOC  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O
7484e256-375a-4897-84c7-7f5d690e710e,train,in  1799  he  took  part  of  the  reduction  of  the  island  of  sri  lanka  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O
0dcca7b2-6103-4359-8aff-f2de4bed4fd4,train,"au  jardin  de  l  enfance  ,  6  pieces  after  l'art  d'être  grand-père  by  victor  hugo  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
32929bec-4985-48bb-8cd9-eb9e6915df49,train,"her  artworks  on  ebay  offer  recreations  of  historic  photographs  ,  each  incorporating  an  implausible  garment  as  the  main  event  . ", O  O  O  B-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
508af1c3-83e8-4d69-b9ff-b995f1f96207,train,"however  ,  it  had  changed  its  shape  to  the  hourglass  silhouette  that  is  even  now  considered  typical  both  for  corsets  and  for  victorian  fashion  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O
7e4bc8aa-6213-4bc4-9744-8021a83ffb9c,train,"on  telegram  ,  a  white  supremacist  channel  encouraged  members  to  distribute  the  propaganda  . ", O  B-CW  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
c7e509be-440e-475a-b13d-57a3401e1081,train,the  commune  is  traversed  by  the  railway  line  from  creil  to  jeumont  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  B-LOC  O
87c2c32e-c792-4a92-bbce-21b0c0f28183,train,"red  dust  ,  directed  by  victor  fleming  ,  starring  jean  harlowová  and  clark  gable ", B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER
2c262d38-4548-4d25-81ed-296f6d1f6f6f,train,a  port  for  ms-dos  also  exists  . , O  O  O  B-CW  O  O  O
8b3e8723-91a2-4c46-bb8f-bce1dacd89c0,train,american  high  commissioner  mark  w.  clark  (  1945  –  1947  ) , O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O
161dda8f-8b5e-4924-b278-2f41ea63125d,train,jordan  also  played  the  ex  boyfriend  in  lily  allen  music  video  smile  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  B-CW  O
1a5cab68-db38-439e-b705-6420e1904396,train,the  station  is  owned  by  cumulus  media  . , O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  O
b8a194e9-d8da-4ab8-982a-9b55f3ec82aa,train,the  race  started  in  compiègne  and  finished  in  roubaix  . , O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  B-LOC  O
ae36c702-3be5-4d0d-9ba4-0cddc9738de0,train,zarm  –  a  lunar  rescue  clone  (  bbc  only  ) , O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  O  O  O  O  O
73a91616-6afa-4d0b-81c1-7e697b8126b9,train,fashion  had  achieved  what  is  now  known  as  the  victorian  fashion  silhouette  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O
3b56dee3-70e2-44e4-8745-8a7dbf6afd9f,train,grange  was  the  first  football  player  to  appear  on  a  box  of  wheaties  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O
bb419df1-210b-459e-89be-2a00fdbf6071,train,he  is  currently  under  a  contract  with  tvb  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  O
167b42da-3641-4ba3-a684-a5f785fc48fd,train,"he  graduated  from  brown  university  in  1822  ,  tutored  there  until  1824  ,  and  then  left  to  study  law  in  windham  ,  connecticut  . ", O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O  B-LOC  O
1877e36a-fdbb-4404-bfb0-4118ef800807,train,it  is  under  the  jurisdiction  of  the  prefecture-level  city  of  anqing  and  contains  its  westernmost  point  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O
1e2ba1bb-1d09-4dba-9dd4-bcf8bd302e1b,train,"shue  starred  in  greyhound  opposite  tom  hanks  ,  released  in  2020  . ", O  O  O  B-CW  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O
13720e7b-e39e-40c5-b0c5-d55b419e1604,train,cream  was  sent  to  the  butter  factory  at  wowan  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O
c81d2dd0-ea77-4bfa-a3c3-d8571bcbfe16,train,"guardians  of  the  galaxy  –  stephane  ceretti  ,  nicolas  aithadi  ,  jonathan  fawkner  ,  and  paul  corbould ", B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  B-PER  I-PER
0238a849-be02-4a9a-b945-e16a3b514fef,train,"by  road  ,  gateshead  can  be  reached  in  under  10  minutes  ,  newcastle  upon  tyne  in  15  minutes  ,  and  newcastle  international  airport  in  25  minutes  . ", O  O  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  I-LOC  I-LOC  O  O  O  O
3f979dfc-30d1-4e1d-b101-2eb45dba9a15,train,"his  films  cheerful  ,  unpretentious  appeal  make  them  the  direct  descendants  of  those  made  a  generation  earlier  by  george  formby  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O
6cc70916-61cd-4cd4-88cc-56f6ca823f12,train,"malone  attended  the  university  of  louisville  ,  where  he  played  baseball  . ", O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  O  O  O  O
78cb424c-185a-4dd8-9328-c1bff2947def,train,mac  powell  –  introduced  the  oh  happy  day  tribute , B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O
acbec4d2-f563-4962-aba1-c135cc67a5c8,train,co  lead  singer  mike  harrison  left  the  band  following  the  release  of  the  album  . , O  O  O  B-PER  I-PER  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
85bac917-622d-441e-bbe7-3300e0c11740,train,"since  the  flavour  and  appeal  largely  depend  on  freshness  ,  commercial  producers  have  to  compensate  by  using  food  additive  as  well  as  imaginative  labeling  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  I-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O
707f50dc-c424-4788-aeab-e47f660e93f1,train,1972  singles  chart  archive  at  the  official  charts  company  (  click  on  relevant  week  ) , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O
d8fc3c30-0147-4337-b6df-3cab0a173484,train,"the  classic  tree  paint  is  black  ,  because  it  is  based  on  an  asphalt  emulsion  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-PROD  O  O
04eba8ac-2a2d-4b5b-a5e0-62876f88e30d,train,the  nearest  major  railway  station  is  at  feroke  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-LOC  O
2e49f339-3caf-413d-a137-854ca8ac474b,train,"digati  put  $  50,000  into  a  variable  life  insurance  policy  by  new  york  life  insurance  company  and  wanted  a  return  of  $  198,303.88  . ", O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  I-CORP  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
1678d0a1-16d9-42d3-92b5-4019a29b3828,train,"because  airliner  fly  at  very  high  altitudes  ,  the  cabin  must  be  pressurized  to  provide  a  safe  quantity  of  breathable  oxygen  to  passengers  and  crew  . ", O  B-PROD  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
966a3784-642c-4ef7-a68d-9d4f2166eadc,train,the  ashmolean  museum  in  oxford  has  a  further  17  landscape  drawings  . , O  B-LOC  I-LOC  O  B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
ab31dc70-280d-4ff5-8367-33c41b1ffb8e,train,"černovice  ,  a  village  (  also  known  as  černovice  u  bukovce  ) ", B-LOC  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O
4e989e15-db7a-446a-9baf-558fba8ed7f0,train,he  is  the  king  of  the  north  according  to  both  the  lesser  key  of  solomon  and  pseudomonarchia  daemonum  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  O  B-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  I-CW  O  B-CW  I-CW  O
8fb0e0e3-cd4e-4d8f-a633-b9fa0313b8c1,train,all  four  of  his  grandparents  were  catholic  church  immigrants  from  germany  . , O  O  O  O  O  O  B-GRP  I-GRP  O  O  B-LOC  O
